

Arne Van Den Kerchove

arne@vandenkerchove.
com
arne.vandenkerchove.
com
+32 473 32 78 71

Dijkstraat 33 2480 Dessel Belgium

Arne Van Den Kerchove

Computer Science Student

About Me I am a motivated Computer Science Student at KU Leuven University. I volunteer in multiple non-profit organisations, both in Leuven and in my home town. My field of interest is large and I love to discover new experiences and places.

Education

2017 - present, KU Leuven University

Master's Degree in Engineering Sciences: Computer Science - Option Artificial Intelligence (Ongoing)

2014 - present, KU Leuven University

Bachelor's Degree in Informatics (Ongoing)

Professional Experience

2016 - present, Freelance Webdeveloper

I am currently a self-employed webdeveloper and webdesigner. I use the Drupal CMS and Django Framework to provide personalized websites to my clients.

May 2015, *Database Refactoring*, Brabantse Apothekers Federatie I was employed to refactor the companies database to a new structure.

June 2014 - August 2014, Front-end Webdeveloper, GBits Webdevelopement

I was employed to design CSS/HTML templates for the DotNetNuke CMS.

Personal Experience

February 2016 - present, Webmaster, Scientica Leuven vzw

I manage the computer systems, software and website of the overarching student association Scientica. I am in control of a multi-server system, primarily used for our member database and student course sale system.

2015 - present, Responsible Person Webteam, Wina Leuven vzw

I lead the technical support team of our student association Wina. I am in charge of a team consisting of 12 volunteers.

2014 - 2018, Vice Responsible Person, Youth Red Cross Retie-Dessel

I am a youth leader in our local youth movement. We are an openly accessible youth movement organise by the Belgian Red Cross, that combines playing with first aid education.

July 2016, Sailing Trainee, The Tall Ships Races

I participated in the 2016 Tall Ships Races. This is an international and multicultural sailing regatta. I worked and lived together with people from different countries while sailing from Antwerp to Lisboa.

Communication Skills

- Native Language: Dutch
- Full Professional Proficiency: English, German
- Minimum Professional Proficiency: French
- Elementary Proficiency: Spanish, Italian



Arne Van Den Kerchove

arne@vandenkerchove.
com
arne.vandenkerchove.
com
+32 473 32 78 71

Dijkstraat 33 2480 Dessel Belgium

Software Development Skills

Programming

- Java
 C, C++
 Python
 Haskell
 PHP
 C#
 Matlab
 Prolog
- JQuery

Computer Software

MySQL
 LaTeX
 HTML,CSS
 Visual Paradigm
 Git,Gitlab CI
 R
 Server stack

Other Qualifications

Animator in Youth Work, Government of Flanders
First Aid Emergency Worker, Belgian Red Cross

Interests

Professional

Artificial intelligence, software design, webdesign and webdevelopment, declarative programming languages, science and engineering.

Personal

Travelling, first aid and Red Cross, books, guitar, biology.